[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "pineapple",
        "back": "ананас"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "jeans",
        "back": "джинсы"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "car",
        "back": "машина"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "fire",
        "back": "огонь"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "room",
        "back": "комната"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "dog",
        "back": "собака"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "cat",
        "back": "кот"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "theater",
        "back": "театр"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "fish",
        "back": "рыба"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "train",
        "back": "поезд"
    }
]